It would appear that our
targets have entered the room.
There are three of them.
The two in the back probably
have bigger builds.
They are avoiding standing
next to any windows or doors.
Judging by their footsteps,
they're definitely pros.
Conrad has sat down on
the sofa next to the wall.
All right, let's have you
hand over the goods.
You'll get your payment after.
I-I'm gonna hold you to your word.
This is definitely MNG data.
All right, as promised...
I've confirmed the deal.
All right. Let's head in...
Yuri.
Roger.
We're with the State Security Service.
You're all under arrest on
suspicion of being spies.
Damn it!
Move!
Good evening, Mister Vile Trash.
We have a wonderful cell
reserved just for you,
so please accompany us
to the station.
Mission and Family
Well done, Second Lieutenant Briar.
Thank you very much.
We need you to take care
of this fellow next.
Have you heard about the various
books and articles going around
in the West that mock and slander Ostania?
It's all nothing but base lies
and conspiracy theories,
and a lot of them are printed
by Ostanian underground presses
and being sold to the West.
And among the writers...
this name popped up.
Franklin Perkin. Age 39.
He was a newspaper reporter during
the previous administration,
and he was arrested for aiding
anti-government extremists.
I want you to follow him and
get the evidence we need,
as well as track down the
buyers of the articles.
As ridiculous as these articles are,
there are plenty of fools in
the West who'll believe them.
I want him dealt with before any
of this influences public opinion.
Yes, sir!
Aren't we working Yuri a bit too hard?
I'll be just fine!
Showing contempt for your own
country for chump change...
I can't even stand the thought of
this filth breathing the same air
as my sister.
Observation of subject
J-095: Franklin Perkin.
On the 6th, subject wakes at 07:21.
Subject watches the television
program Good Morning Ostania.
Subject curses at the newscaster.
08:10, subject leaves
for job at post office.
See appendices for details of his attire.
Subject rides on third car of U-8 train.
See appendices for descriptions
of fellow passengers.
At 12:06, subject goes to the
restaurant Fjord with coworker M.
Orders lunch Set A.
See appendices for log
of conversation topics.
At 17:49, subject leaves work
and goes to central market.
At noon today,
the 12th Annual International Education
Symposium was held in Frejis.
Sonia... were you deceiving me?
At 18:33, subject returns home
No, no! You're the only one I love, Vincent!
and watches television programs
News 20 and Berlint in Love.
Subject appears infatuated
with the female lead.
Then why—
To prove my love—
No further activities of note
before retiring for the night.
You sure didn't hold back on the details.
Leave this to me!
You've been at this for
two days without sleep.
Switch out with someone
else and get some rest.
Oh, this is nothing.
This is the report for the next day.
"On the 7th, at 08:07,
subject goes to work."
"Has lunch at the restaurant
Fjord and orders lunch Set B..."
"Fjord."
"Yor."
You're tired. Go rest.
No. That always happens.
Mister Perkin! Mister Perkin,
you're home, aren't you?
H-Hey there, Ms. Landlady.
Could you pay me the rent
you're late on already?
Could you wait just a little longer?
You said the same thing last time.
The day after tomorrow! I promise
to pay you the day after tomorrow!
If you're lying again, I'll really
throw you out this time.
Stupid landlady.
Dad, I'm heading out for a bit.
I made some food, so eat whenever you want.
All right. See you later.
Is he being cautious of anyone following him?
Or he's looking for something
to write in his article.
Our country must face this with resolve!
Yeah! That's right!
Let's teach the West a lesson!
I can't get any decent pictures.
Yay! I got a Bondman replica
pistol as a present!
No fair! Let me see it!
No way!
Meanie!
Huh? Hey!
My pistol!
Overcome by poverty,
street children desperately
dig through trash for scraps.
Not bad.
What's the big idea, you stupid geezer?!
We're gonna tell the Secret Police on you!
You little miser who keeps his wealth for
himself and doesn't share it with others.
People whose ideals lean toward
the West, like yourself...
are the ones who are going to get arrested
and killed.
That bastard!
I'm gonna execute him!
Don't.
Let him go until we find out who's
buying his underground publications.
This article should make some people laugh.
Frank.
Dad.
You'd better not be doing
any dangerous work again.
I-I'm not. Go away.
If you didn't have your odd sense of justice,
you'd have been able to keep
your job at the paper.
What's so wrong about trying to improve
the country my family lives in?
Even now... we need money just to
keep up this lousy living situation.
If we had money, Mom would've...
Frank, you...
It's nothing. Damn it all!
On the 11th at 08:36,
subject leaves for work.
He had no suspicious contacts or interactions
that may lead to the buyer while
at home or while he was out.
Which means...
It must be his place of work.
Here's all the mail that's been inspected.
Thanks!
Good work.
Hey, Joseph. I'll take care of these.
Go ahead and take your lunch break.
Oh, hey. Thanks.
What should I get for lunch?
So he was boldly mailing them after
slipping through inspection.
If you go through with mailing that...
You won't be able to talk
your way out of this.
On the 15th at 08:02.
I'm heading to work.
Mm.
The State Security... Service.
Sorry, Dad. I might not be back for a while.
Franklin Perkin.
You are the one who wrote this, are you not?
We've already captured
the buyer addressed here.
Surrender.
You really bothered to wait outside for me.
What kind State Security Service officers.
It's so your family doesn't have
to see how pathetic you are.
Don't get the wrong idea.
Me, who fought the government,
and you, the government's dog...
I wonder who's really the pathetic one here.
I would never do anything
to make my family sad.
Never.
I'll request that your father gets
some financial aid to get by.
Thanks.
Hello there, Yuri!
Chief!
You've been working hard!
I'm happy to hear it.
I'm honored, sir.
This must be rather difficult
work for a newbie.
Don't let the stress build up.
Oh, no.
I think I'm quite well-suited for this job!
I'll use this momentum to capture Twilight
and protect the peace of this nation!
I see. I hope that's the case.
I'll treat you to a good meal sometime.
Something with plenty of meat.
Really?! I'm going to hold you to that, sir!
Coming!
Hiya, Sis!
Yuri?! What brings you here so late?
Unkie.
Good evening, Yuri.
Grr! Why are you here, Loid Forger?!
You should stay at work, even at night!
Did something happen?
I just felt like seeing you, Sis.
What do you want, stupid leash girl?
Good job at work today.
I'll get some tea ready for you.
Sis, Sis...
Yor
Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis,
Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis...
Sis!
Blech...
Come, now. You're going to
disturb the neighbors, Yuri.
The Elegant Bondman
My name is Bondman!
Leave this to me and run on ahead, Agent M!
No!
I don't want to lose you!
M...
I'll follow you to the ends
of the earth, Bondman.
We're getting out of here!
My spotless suit.
My beloved, gleaming silver car.
The techniques I mastered through countless
battles, and my gentlemanly demeanor...
Oh, you're such a masterful driver!
I love you, Bondman!
Because I'm the coolest and so
clever, romance comes naturally.
I work as a spy in a country
you consider an enemy.
Get in my way and I'll
make sure you regret it!
How foolish.
We're of the same species
and live on the same planet.
Why do we need to fight over
something as petty as a boundary?
In that case, why don't you
try and stop this conflict?!
The peace treaty has been signed!
Now nothing can stand in our way!
You're amazing, Bondman!
I'll never let you go!
My father's obsessed with
creating this Destroyer Bomb!
Please stop him, Bondman!
But of course, Gina!
Oh... Thank you so much, Bondman!
Once my father wakes up,
I want to introduce you to him!
Glad to hear it, Gina!
My terrorist lover was arrested because of you!
You won't get away with this!
Revenge will only make you sadder.
I'll make you forget about
all that with my love.
Our organization's goal is
to take over the world!
Never mind all that. Let's go out on a date.
Mister Bondman, please pay this month's rent.
Also, there are noise complaints
from the neighbors.
Hello there! You're as beautiful
as ever, Ms. Landlady.
Hey! What's with all these broads?!
Pick one already, damn it!
Huh?
How many of us are you dating?!
You cheater!
I'm going to make every last
lady in this world happy!
Dealing with risk is just
part of a spy's job...
Spy Wars! Next time, "Bondman Returns!!"
I see. So this is what a flirting story is like.
Now I can discuss this with Becky.
Anya has become an adult.
Don't do that.
How was anything he did gentlemanly?
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
Extra I
The Heart of a Child I
On the Department Store Roof
Anya wants to ride Mister Polar Bear.
I cannot comprehend what is
so entertaining about this
mysterious means of transportation
called "Polar Bear."
Why do children insist on riding this thing?
It's clearly boring and not exhilarating.
Plus, it almost seems
like a corrective device
created by an authoritarian regime
to steal the emotions of the passenger
and change them into a
mindless puppet and—
I wanna ride it!
Let's let her ride it, Loid.
Was that fun?
I gotta ride it again!
I don't understand children.
Extra II
The Heart of a Child II
The Silt Seashore is packed with people
wanting to enjoy various seaside activities.
Anya wants to go to the ocean.
We can't go to the ocean, but I can
at least take you to the pool.
Pool!
I'm so glad she seems to be having fun.
Aw, man, I just peed. Not like
anyone's going to find out.
* Don't try this at home, boys and girls
I feel so much better.
I never want to go to the pool again.
Huh?! But she looked like
she was having so much fun!
I don't understand children.
Extra III
Waking Up
Lord Damian, you need to get up,
or you'll be late to roll call.
Huh?
Lord Damian!
You were already awake?
Yeah, about an hour ago.
I was reviewing some things.
Me oversleeping last week
was just by chance.
Impressive as ever!
Wake up, Anya!
You've only got ten minutes
until your bus gets here!
Anya has ten more minutes
until the explosion...
Anya will stop it...
Come on, wake up!
If you keep going in late,
you're going to get a Tonitrus Bolt!
She was late
The Pastry of Knowledge
The Informant's Great Romance Plan II